(Leonard:)I'm sorry, don't
listen to him.
(Leonard:)We're actually
physicists.
(Leonard:)We're giving a lecture
at Berkeley later today.
(Leonard:)We just... we had
some time to kill.
GUARD: Hey, listen, you
seem like decent guys.
(Security Guard:)I can't let you in,
(Security Guard:)but I got some hats and T-shirts
I can give you.
(Leonard:)Thank you so much.
(Leonard:)See?
(Leonard:)Maybe honesty is the best...
(door opens)
(Leonard:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Shedding the yoke
of my oppressors,
(Sheldon:)you blind,
sad little man.
Don't move!
(Security Guard:)Code A-A-23, A-A-23.
GUARD 2:
Copy.
SHELDON (gasps):
I can see the ranch, Leonard!
(Sheldon:)Oh, it's rustic,
it's lovely.
(Sheldon:)I'd take a picture,
but people are chasing me.
I'm gonna make it...!
I'm gonna make it!
(Sheldon:)They have Tasers,
but they wouldn't dare use...
(Sheldon screams)
(thuds)
(Howard:)Come on, Raj.
(Howard:)You are the King Kong
of Ping-Pong.
(Howard:)You are the menace
of table tennis.